Are you shy? Does this embarrass you? Are you thinking that people will notice your
new accent and criticize you for it? In the beginning, you may feel a little
strange with these new sounds that you're using, but don't worry, it's like a new
pair of shoes. They take a while to break in and make comfortable. Nevertheless, I
hope that you're enjoying this program. Adopting a new accent can become too
personal and too emotional an issue, so don't take it too seriously. Relax. Have a
good time. Play with the sounds that you're making. Whenever a word or phrase
strikes your fancy, go somewhere private and comfortable and try out a couple
different approaches, styles, and attitudes with it, as you're going to do
in the next exercise. If possible, record yourself on tape so you can decide which
one suits you best.